Let's get started writing some queries.
我们来开始写些查询吧
First, we're going to generate a list of
首先 我们要生成一张列表
all the orders that Parch and Posey has ever received.
记录 Parch &amp; Posey 曾接下的所有订单
It's a simple but valuable way to learn a bit more about the company.
很简单 但也是个很好的办法 可以更深入地了解这家公司
Parch and Posey records their orders in a table called Orders.
Parch &amp; Posey 把订单记录在一张叫 Orders (订单) 的表里
That table contains all the columns you see here,
在这你可以看到那张表的所有列
each of which corresponds to some attribute and order.
每列就相当于订单的某项属性
Each order has a unique ID,
每笔订单都有唯一的 ID
so that it can be referenced and a time stamp to indicate when that order was placed.
可用于索引 还有一个时间戳 记录了下订单的时间
It also contains quantity sold and revenue generated for each type of paper ordered.
还包括每种纸的销售数量和所得营收
In order to generate the list of all orders,
为了生成这张记录着所有订单的列表
we'll write a SELECT statement.
我们要写一个 SELECT 语句
Think of a SELECT statement as
可以把 SELECT 语句想成
filling out a form to get the results you're trying to get.
一张要填的表格 填完表你就能得到想要的结果
The form has a set of questions like,
这张表格里有一系列问题 如
what data do you want to pull from?
你想从什么数据里调出信息？
And which elements of that data set do you want to pull?
你想从那个数据集里调出什么元素？
These questions are structured in the same order every time.
这些问题每次都以相同的顺序呈现
Some of them are mandatory and others are optional.
有些是必填项 有些则是可选项
When writing out the SELECT statement,
在写 SELECT 语句的时候
each of these questions is represented by a single word like SELECT or FROM.
这些问题会被换成一些简单的词 如 SELECT 或 FROM
These words are called clauses.
这些词称为子句
The FROM clause tells the query what data to use.
FROM 子句告诉查询要使用什么数据
Here, we're looking at the Orders table.
我们这里需要订单表
So I'll write that in after FROM.
所以我在 FROM 后写下该表的名字
The SELECT clause tells the query which columns to read from that table.
SELECT 子句告诉查询要从那个表里读取哪些列
Column names are separated by commas with no comma needed after the last column name.
列名由逗号隔开 最后一个列名后无需加逗号
You can also select all of the column names using
你也可以选择所有列名
Select with an asterisk where the asterisk means all.
方法是在 Select 后加星号 星号意味着所有
People typically say this as select star.
通常人们会把星号叫作选择星号
Both the SELECT and FROM clauses are mandatory.
SELECT 和 FROM 子句都是必填项
You'll include them in every query you write as part of this course.
本课中你要写的每个查询都要用到它们
If you do not include both of them,
如果你漏掉了两者之一
you'll get an error message instead of the desired results.
你就得不到想要的结果 只会得到出错提示
When I click run, the database will execute this query and return the results,
点击运行 数据库就会执行这个查询并返回结果
every row in the Orders table showing all available columns.
订单表的每一行都会把可访问的所有列显示出来
Now that you've seen this,
看完这些操作
you already have enough knowledge to do something valuable.
你已经具备足够的知识去做一些有价值的事了
You can read a table,
你可以读取表
and if you'd like,
并且如果你想的话
export your results to view them in another application like Excel.
还可以把结果导出到 Excel 等应用里 进行查看